[This drama is fictional and any similarity with reality is purely coincidental.]
[이 드라마는 허구이며 어떠한 유사성도 있습니다. 현실은 순전히 우연이다.]
[Production guidelines were followed when filming children and animals.]
[생산 지침을 따랐습니다. 어린이나 동물을 촬영할 때.]
She is really precious to me.
그녀는 나에게 정말 소중합니다.
[Episode 10] So I can't lie to deny her.
[10화] 그래서 나는 그녀를 부정하기 위해 거짓말을 할 수 없습니다.
It's okay if you doubt me and criticize me.
나를 의심하고 비난해도 괜찮습니다.
But please refrain from excessive criticism
하지만 지나친 비난은 자제해주세요
or speculation about them.
또는 그에 대한 추측.
I sincerely request this.
진심으로 요청드립니다.
According to him, they are actually in love.
그에 따르면 그들은 실제로 사랑에 빠졌습니다.
Why did you do that?
왜 그랬어요?
I told you to hide it.
숨기라고 했어요.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
But even if I went back,
하지만 다시 돌아간다고 해도
I probably would do the same.
아마 나도 똑같이 할 것입니다.
I don't want to act as if you and our Yeol Mu never happened.
난 너처럼 행동하고 싶지 않아 그리고 우리 열무는 그런 일이 없었어요.
This is my choice too.
이것도 내 선택이다.
I knew it wouldn't be easy when I started,
처음엔 쉽지 않을 거라는 걸 알았지만,
so rather than regretting that choice,
그러니 그 선택을 후회하기보다는
I want to do my best in whatever I can do.
나는 내가 할 수 있는 일에 최선을 다하고 싶다.
Thanks for worrying about me.
걱정해주셔서 감사합니다.
I'll get through this.
나는 이것을 극복할 것이다.
You know I'm strong in a crisis.
나는 위기에 강하다는 걸 당신도 알잖아요.
I watched the press conference.
기자회견을 봤습니다.
I thought you were impressive,
당신이 인상적이라고 생각했는데,
even as a man.
남자로서도.
Anyone would do that to protect someone they care about.
누구라도 그럴텐데 소중한 사람을 보호하기 위해.
Is that so?
그렇습니까?
It seems that stubborn Hui Won
완고한 희원인 것 같다.
needs someone like you who could bear all that.
당신 같은 사람이 필요해요 그 모든 것을 견딜 수 있는 사람.
Someone who can protect her
그녀를 지켜줄 수 있는 사람
in any situation.
어떤 상황에서도.
Please take good care of Hui Won.
희원님 잘 보살펴주세요.
[The greatest romantic of our time] President Kang Du Jun,
[우리 시대 최고의 로맨티스트] 강두준 회장님,
ascends as the greatest romantic of our time.
우리 시대 최고의 낭만주의자로 떠오른다.
The way this man loves.
이 남자가 사랑하는 방식.
[The way he loves, I'll take the criticism] I will take the criticism.
[그가 사랑하는 방식에 대한 비판은 내가 받겠다] 비판은 받아들이겠습니다.
Even as a man, I admit it.
남자인 저도 인정합니다.
I was really surprised.
정말 놀랐어요.
Instead of an explanation, he actually confessed.
설명 대신, 그는 실제로 고백했다.
As expected of the President.
대통령의 예상대로.
The video views totally exploded too.
영상 조회수도 완전 폭발했어요.
When I checked this morning, the public opinion seems to have swung,
오늘 아침에 확인해보니, 여론이 급락한 것 같다.
and the stock has recovered a lot.
그리고 주가가 많이 회복됐어요.
Honestly, isn't this basically like proposing,
솔직히 원래 이런거 아닌가 제안하듯이,
saying 'I love you' in front of the whole country?
'사랑해요'라고 말하면서 전국 앞에서?
When will I ever get a proposal like that?
언제쯤 그런 제안을 받을 수 있을까요?
Try hinting at it to your boyfriend.
남자친구에게 힌트를 주어보세요.
We broke up.
우리는 헤어졌다.
- Again?
- 다시?
Wasn't this supposed to be true love this time?
이거 그럴 뻔 한거 아니었어? 이번엔 진짜 사랑이 될까?
It wasn't true love.
그것은 진정한 사랑이 아니었습니다.
It was triple love, triple love.
삼중 사랑, 삼중 사랑이었습니다.
I thought he was a caring, warm-hearted person.
배려심이 깊은 사람인 줄 알았는데 마음이 따뜻한 사람.
But he was taking care of his ex and even his ex-ex.
하지만 그 사람은 전 애인을 돌보고 있었어 심지어 그의 전 애인까지요.
Oh, Manager Jang.
아, 장과장님.
Sit here for a moment.
잠시 여기 앉아보세요.
Manager, did you see yesterday's press conference?
매니저님, 보셨나요? 어제 기자회견?
I want to be his number one fan.
나는 그의 최고의 팬이 되고 싶다.
Ah, I had some business yesterday, so...
아, 어제 일이 있어서...
The President must have been really impressive.
대통령은 반드시 정말 인상적이었어요.
Who on earth is the woman the President is seeing?
여자는 도대체 누구야? 대통령이 보고 계시나요?
I'm jealous.
나는 질투한다.
She must have saved the country in her past life.
그 사람이 저장한 게 틀림없어 전생의 나라.
Just the country?
그냥 나라?
She probably saved the whole world.
그녀는 아마도 전 세계를 구했을 것입니다.
I think that person must be just as impressive as the President.
내 생각엔 그 사람이 꼭 그런 사람일 것 같아 대통령만큼이나 인상적이다.
Se Hyeon, do you know something?
세현아, 뭔가 알아?
You talk like you've met her.
당신은 그녀를 만난 것처럼 이야기합니다.
Oh, come on, do you have to see someone to know?
아, 그러세요? 아는 사람을 만나야 해?
Just the look in the President's eyes, the tremor in his voice
대통령의 눈빛만 보아도 그의 목소리의 떨림
when he talks about her.
그가 그녀에 대해 말할 때.
It tells you everything.
그것은 당신에게 모든 것을 알려줍니다.
The President being impressive is one thing,
대통령이 인상적인 것은,
but we also have to work impressively.
하지만 우리는 또한 인상적으로 일해야 합니다.
To the conference room in 10 minutes.
10분 안에 회의실로 가세요.
Understood.
이해했다.
[President Kang Du Jun ascends as the greatest romantic of our time]
[강두준 회장 취임 우리 시대 최고의 낭만가로서]
I think our team is forming a Kang Du Jun fan club.
우리 팀이 형성되고 있는 것 같아요 강두준 팬클럽
Seems like you are not just impressive to my eyes.
당신은 그렇지 않은 것 같아요 내 눈에는 인상적이다.
I think so too.
저도 그렇게 생각합니다.
Yes.
그렇습니다.
It's not over yet.
아직 끝나지 않았습니다.
The real beginning starts now.
진짜 시작은 지금부터입니다.
Even if public opinion has turned, it wasn't an action worthy of praise.
여론이 바뀌어도 칭찬받을 만한 행동은 아니었습니다.
It was a risky move.
그것은 위험한 움직임이었습니다.
The stock price hasn't fully recovered yet either.
주가는 그렇지 않았다 아직 완전히 회복됐어요.
I know.
알아요.
I will take responsibility until the damages are fully restored.
내가 책임지겠다 피해가 완전히 복구될 때까지.
You'll need to pay even more attention going forward.
더 많은 비용을 지불해야 합니다. 앞으로 주목.
Still, it falls far short of the qualifications of a true entrepreneur.
그래도 아직은 많이 부족해요 진정한 기업가의 자격.
But in terms of making the company approachable to the public,
하지만 회사를 만드는 측면에서는 대중에게 다가갈 수 있는,
it wasn't a bad choice.
나쁜 선택은 아니었어요.
After all, a company is made up of people.
결국 회사는 사람으로 구성됩니다.
Her name is Jang Hui Won, right?
이름이 장희원 맞죠?
Father, how did you...
아버지, 어떻게 지내셨나요...
She's the woman you're so determined to protect.
그 사람이 바로 당신의 여자예요 그래서 보호하기로 결심했습니다.
Go arrange it.
가서 준비하세요.
Let's have a meal together.
같이 식사하자.
Yes.
예.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
The thing you did to wreck his image
그의 이미지를 망가뜨리기 위해 당신이 한 일
ended up making him likable!
결국 그를 좋아하게 만들었습니다!
What are you going to do now?
이제 무엇을 할 건가요?
Do you have a backup plan?
백업 계획이 있나요?
How many times do I have to spell it out for you?
나는 몇 번이나 당신을 위해 그것을 철자해야합니까?
If you're so anxious and dissatisfied, just step away from this.
너무 불안하고 불만족스러우시다면 그냥 여기서 물러나세요.
I don't care either way.
나는 어느 쪽이든 상관하지 않습니다.
No, I'm just concerned.
아뇨, 그냥 걱정이에요.
I told you there's a plan B.
플랜 B가 있다고 말했잖아요.
Kang Du Jun has been on psychiatric medication for over ten years.
강두준은 10년 넘게 정신과 약물 치료를 받아왔다.
Yet he still can't shake hands during external meetings
그런데 그 사람은 아직도 악수를 못해요. 외부 회의 중
or over important contracts.
또는 중요한 계약을 통해.
Instead of coming here constantly, why not manage the board members?
여기 꾸준히 오는 것보다는 왜 이사회 구성원을 관리하지 않습니까?
Can you handle that?
감당할 수 있나요?
Yes, of course.
물론이죠.
I'll take care of the board.
보드는 제가 처리하겠습니다.
Of course, I'll take care of it.
물론이죠. 제가 처리하겠습니다.
[Han Jeong Eum]
[한정음]
No.
아니요.
No, baby.
아니, 자기야.
Baby, no.
자기야, 아니야.
[Han Jeong Eum]
[한정음]
[Non-alcoholic beer is evolving into a new beverage category]
[무알콜 맥주가 진화하고 있다 새로운 음료 카테고리로]
Manager Jang, working late again today?
장과장님 오늘도 야근하세요?
Because of that contest?
그 대회 때문에?
Yes, I had a sudden idea, so I'll wrap this up before leaving.
응, 갑자기 그런 생각이 들었어. 그러니 떠나기 전에 이걸 마무리하겠습니다.
Hey, working this hard alone makes me feel guilty as a teammate.
야 혼자서 이렇게 열심히 일해 팀원으로서 죄책감을 느끼게 만든다.
I'm doing it because I enjoy it.
나는 그것을 즐기기 때문에 그것을하고 있습니다.
I'll share everything anyway.
어쨌든 모든 것을 공유하겠습니다.
Then let's work together.
그럼 함께 일합시다.
It'll finish quickly together.
같이 하면 빨리 끝나요.
Ah, no.
아, 아니.
I'll finish this quickly and head home soon too.
빨리 끝내겠습니다 그리고 너도 빨리 집으로 가.
So go ahead.
그러니 계속하세요.
It's fine, you go first.
괜찮아요, 먼저 가세요.
Make sure to share it, okay?
꼭 공유해 보세요, 알았죠?
Youngest managers aren't made overnight.
막내 관리자는 하루아침에 만들어지지 않습니다.
See you tomorrow.
내일 봐요.
Wow, I feel ashamed.
와, 부끄럽네요.
What?
무엇?
- Still... - It's okay.
- 아직도... - 괜찮아요.
Go quickly.
빨리 가세요.
Then, fighting!
그럼 화이팅!
- Fighting! - See you tomorrow.
- 화이팅! - 내일 봐요.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
응, 내일 보자.
[Non-alcoholic beer is evolving into a new beverage category]
[무알콜 맥주가 진화하고 있다 새로운 음료 카테고리로]
Is she very busy?
그 사람 많이 바쁜가요?
You're probably crazy to see her, huh?
아마 그 사람을 보면 정말 미칠 것 같죠?
You scared me, jeez.
겁을 줬잖아, 이런.
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Team Leader Bang?
방 팀장?
Who else would I come to see?
내가 또 누구를 만나러 올 것인가?
Team Leader Bang is a charming woman.
방 팀장은 매력적인 여성이다.
Hey, how did you know?
이봐, 어떻게 알았어?
I know you inside out.
나는 당신을 속속들이 알고 있습니다.
If you're dating, why can't you just say it?
사귄다면 왜 그냥 말을 못하냐?
Then I'll head out first.
그럼 나 먼저 나가볼게.
How dare you leave before me?
어떻게 감히 나보다 먼저 떠나?
I haven't even left work yet.
아직 퇴근도 안했어요.
Si Hyeong, please go buy some late-night snacks for Hui Won.
시형아 꼭 사러가라 희원을 위한 야식.
- Hey! - For Team Leader Bang too.
- 여기요! - 방 팀장에게도요.
What would they like, both of them?
둘 다 무엇을 원할까요?
Card, card!
카드야, 카드야!
You're really gonna be rich, huh?
너 정말 부자가 될 거야, 응?
Buy a lot.
많이 사세요.
[Global & domestic non-alcoholic beer market] Manager.
[글로벌 및 국내 무알콜 맥주 시장] 매니저.
Se Hyeon too.
세현도.
Wow, Manager Jang.
와, 장과장님.
Seeing it again, non-alcoholic is really nice.
다시 보니, 무알콜 정말 맛있어요.
- Really? - Yeah.
- 정말? - 응.
When did you do all this?
언제 이런 짓을 다 했어?
Manager, this is incredible.
매니저님, 정말 말도 안 돼요.
You're not complimenting me for no reason, right?
당신은 나를 칭찬하지 않습니다 아무 이유 없이 그렇죠?
No, no. Our team is a complete dream team.
아니, 아니. 우리 팀은 완전한 드림팀이다.
If you're free this weekend, let's meet my parents.
이번 주말에 시간이 되신다면 부모님을 만나자.
I've got a family, so I can't join you, which is such a shame.
가족이 있어서 함께 할 수가 없어요. 정말 부끄러운 일입니다.
How did you manage this?
이것을 어떻게 관리했습니까?
Huh?
뭐?
President.
대통령.
Please sit, please sit.
앉아주세요, 앉아주세요.
Oh.
오.
[Flavor stabilization, reduced astringent aftertaste]
[향미안정화, 떫은 뒷맛 감소]
[The new value of non-alcoholic beer]
[무알콜 맥주의 새로운 가치]
Good morning.
좋은 아침입니다.
Yes, good morning.
네, 좋은 아침이에요.
Manager Jang. Did you come early? Or pull an all-nighter?
장 매니저님. 일찍 왔나요? 아니면 밤새도록 하시겠습니까?
It's a secret.
비밀이에요.
Ah, Manager. Have some coffee.
아, 매니저님. 커피를 마셔보세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Can I drink this instead?
대신 이걸 마셔도 될까요?
- Sure. - I'll enjoy it.
- 확신하는. - 즐기겠습니다.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
- Yes. - Hi.
- 예. - 안녕.
Assistant Manager Choi, hair roller.
헤어롤러 최 대리.
- Want to borrow it? - No, It's fine.
- 빌릴래? - 아뇨, ​​괜찮아요.
- Tak Soo. - Yes.
-탁수. - 예.
Make sure to eat lunch while working.
일하는 동안 점심을 꼭 드세요.
Working hard is good, but think about me sometimes too.
열심히 일하는 것은 좋은 일이다. 하지만 가끔은 내 생각도 해주세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
But is it really this hard to go on a date once?
그런데 정말 이렇게 힘든 걸까 데이트 한번 해볼까?
There isn't much time left to submit the contest.
시간이 많이 남지 않았어 콘테스트를 제출합니다.
Please bear with me for a few days.
며칠만 참아주세요.
I know you're more ambitious than anyone.
나는 당신이 누구보다 야망이 크다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
But I'm worried you might get sick from overworking.
하지만 네가 그럴까봐 걱정돼 과로로 아프다.
I didn't plan to push this far.
이렇게까지 밀어붙일 생각은 아니었어요.
But as I prepared, I became ambitious.
그런데 준비하면서 욕심이 생겼어요.
After giving up studying in Germany,
독일 유학을 포기한 후,
I wondered when I'd get another chance like this.
언제 받을지 궁금했는데 또 이런 기회가.
I thought maybe this contest
아마 이번 대회가 아닐까 생각했어요
could be that chance.
그 기회가 될 수도 있어요.
A brand bearing my name, the next Try Beer.
내 이름을 딴 브랜드, 다음은 Try Beer입니다.
Just thinking about it makes me excited.
생각만 해도 설레네요.
Oh, it's not like I'm asking for special treatment for no reason.
아 제가 묻는 건 아닌데 이유 없이 특별 대우를 받기 위해
Don't misunderstand.
오해하지 마세요.
I was planning to step out of judging anyway.
어차피 심사에서 물러날 생각이었거든요.
If our relationship gets out later,
나중에 우리 관계가 밝혀지면
it could cause unnecessary gossip.
불필요한 소문이 생길 수 있습니다.
So for this contest, just do everything you want to do without holding back.
그러니까 이번 대회는 뭐든지 다 해라 거침없이 하고 싶다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Oh, and by the way, are you free this weekend?
아, 그런데, 이번 주말에 시간 있어?
My parents suggested we have a casual meal together.
부모님이 제안하셨어요 우리는 함께 캐주얼한 식사를 해요.
Oh.
오.
If you feel pressured, you can decline.
압박감을 느끼면 거절해도 됩니다.
We can do it another time when we have the chance.
다음에 하자 기회가 있을 때.
Sounds good.
좋은 것 같아요.
They'd probably be curious.
그들은 아마 궁금해할 것입니다.
Please set it up.
설정해주세요.
I'll properly introduce myself to them.
나는 그들에게 내 자신을 제대로 소개할 것이다.
Is this too conservative?
너무 보수적인가?
Or maybe too drab?
아니면 너무 단조로운가요?
Then this one...
그럼 이건...
Hey, Jang Hui Won.
안녕하세요, 장희원님.
I knew you'd be like this.
나는 당신이 이럴 것이라는 것을 알았습니다.
You still haven't picked your outfit?
아직도 옷을 고르지 못하셨나요?
Look.
바라보다.
Is this better? Or this one?
이게 더 나은가요? 아니면 이거?
I guess I should skip tight clothes now that my belly's showing more, right?
꽉 끼는 옷은 피해야 할 것 같아요 이제 배가 더 많이 보이잖아요?
You're wearing this to meet your future in-laws?
이거 입고 있잖아 미래의 친척을 만나러?
I must have been out of my mind then.
그때 나는 정신이 나갔었나 보다.
Why did I agree to go?
내가 왜 가기로 동의했습니까?
Look at this one.
이것 좀 보세요.
How about this dress?
이 드레스 어때요?
- Stylish, right? - Not at all.
- 스타일리시하죠? - 별말씀을요.
Absolutely not.
절대 그렇지 않습니다.
Take that off and follow me.
그거 벗고 날 따라오세요.
Hey, wait!
잠깐만요!
Hello, Director.
안녕하세요, 감독님.
- Hello.
- 안녕하세요.
Today, my friend must look elegant yet graceful,
오늘은 친구가 꼭 해야 할 일 우아하면서도 우아한 느낌,
clear yet vivid,
선명하면서도 생생하게,
and finally with a touch of lovely, juicy charm.
그리고 마지막으로 사랑스러운 터치로, 육즙이 많은 매력.
You know what I mean, right?
무슨 말인지 아시죠?
Isn't that too much?
너무 많은 것 아닌가?
Do you know how many couples got married after just one touch from her?
커플이 몇명인지 아시나요? 그녀의 손길 한 번만에 결혼했다고?
Please start. I'm counting on you.
시작해주세요. 나는 당신을 믿고 있습니다.
Carry my bag. I'm so nervous.
내 가방을 들어라. 너무 긴장돼요.
You've waited long, haven't you?
오래 기다리셨죠?
Shall we go?
갈까요?
Why?
왜?
Is it too much after all?
결국 너무 많은 걸까요?
You look so beautiful.
당신은 정말 아름다워 보여요.
You've always been this beautiful.
당신은 항상 이렇게 아름다웠어요.
But if you keep getting prettier every day, how am I supposed to handle it?
하지만 매일매일 계속 예뻐진다면 어떻게 처리해야 하나요?
Ah, you're exaggerating.
아, 과장하시는군요.
I don't know. Let's hurry.
모르겠습니다. 서두르자.
No, not exaggeration. I'm speaking from the heart.
아니요, 과장이 아닙니다. 나는 마음에서 말하고 있습니다.
Hurry up. They're waiting.
서둘러요. 그들은 기다리고 있습니다.
But aren't you nervous at all?
그런데 전혀 긴장되지 않나요?
I'm nervous. I'm shaking like crazy. Come on.
긴장돼요. 미친 듯이 떨고 있어요. 어서 해봐요.
Why are you so nervous?
왜 그렇게 긴장해요?
Was the trip here difficult?
여기 여행이 힘들었나요?
And are you feeling okay physically?
그리고 몸은 괜찮아요?
Yes, I'm fine.
네, 괜찮아요.
Thank you for your concern.
걱정해 주셔서 감사합니다.
I felt a bit uneasy sending you off like that last time.
좀 불안한 느낌이 들었어 저번에도 그렇게 보냈어요.
Please take it as meddling from parents who lost a child.
간섭으로 받아들여주세요 아이를 잃은 부모로부터.
Not at all.
별말씀을요.
I completely understand.
나는 완전히 이해합니다.
What do you mean, last time?
지난번에 무슨 말이야?
Father, have you met Hui Won before?
아버님, 희원님을 만난 적이 있나요?
Only she and I know about this secret.
이 비밀은 나와 그녀만이 알고 있다.
You don't need to know.
알 필요는 없습니다.
How can that be? You didn't even tell me.
어떻게 그럴 수 있습니까? 당신은 나에게 말하지도 않았습니다.
Anyway, since you're pregnant, shouldn't you take a break from work?
아무튼 임신 중이니까 일 좀 쉬어야 하지 않나?
- Pardon? - Hui Won is exceptionally capable.
- 뭐라고요? - 희원은 유난히 능력이 뛰어나다.
So she has a lot on her plate.
그래서 그녀는 접시에 많은 것을 가지고 있습니다.
Did I ask you?
내가 물어 봤나요?
I'm worried it might be hard since she's carrying a child.
힘들지 않을까 걱정이에요 그녀가 아이를 안고 있으니까요.
Does the company know about the pregnancy?
회사에서는 임신 사실을 알고 있나요?
We want to take it slow on that.
우리는 그것에 대해 천천히 진행하고 싶습니다.
They don't know yet.
그들은 아직 모릅니다.
Why not?
왜 안 돼?
Is there some reason you can't reveal it?
공개할 수 없는 이유가 있나요?
Does she need a reason?
이유가 필요합니까?
It's probably because their relationship is still a secret.
아마도 그 이유는 그들의 관계는 여전히 비밀이다.
I'm just asking because I'm curious.
그냥 궁금해서 물어보는 거에요.
Because I know nothing about this young lady.
왜냐하면 나는 이 젊은 아가씨에 대해 아무것도 모르기 때문이다.
Given the nature of our work, pregnant employees often get reduced workloads.
업무 특성상 임신 중 직원들은 업무량이 줄어드는 경우가 많습니다.
Or get removed from projects.
아니면 프로젝트에서 제거됩니다.
Even when stepping back,
뒤로 물러나는 순간에도,
I want to wrap things up as much as possible.
가능한 한 모든 것을 마무리하고 싶습니다.
This is all out of consideration for the team.
이건 다 고려사항이 아니다 팀을 위해.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Excuse me, it's a bit chilly in here.
죄송합니다만, 여기가 좀 추워요.
Could you raise the temperature?
온도 좀 올려주실 수 있나요?
Yes, one moment.
네, 잠시만요.
Um, here.
음, 여기요.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
I was a bit cold.
나는 조금 추웠다.
Actually, I was cold too.
사실 나도 추웠어.
Thanks to you, it feels so warm and comfortable.
덕분에 기분이 좋아지네요 너무 따뜻하고 편안해요.
Okay, let's dig in.
좋아, 자세히 살펴보자.
Yes, I'll enjoy it.
네, 즐겨보겠습니다.
Was it tiring today?
오늘은 피곤했나요?
It was fun. They were both really nice.
재미있었습니다. 둘 다 정말 친절했어요.
I apologize for my mom being irritable earlier.
엄마한테 사과해요 일찍부터 짜증이 난다.
She's not normally like that, but today...
평소엔 그렇지 않은데 오늘은...
It's because she cares about you so much.
그 사람이 당신을 너무 걱정하기 때문이죠.
She wants her son to be with a good woman. That's why she acts that way.
그녀는 아들이 좋은 여자와 함께 있기를 원합니다. 그래서 그녀는 그렇게 행동합니다.
Where else can I find a woman as good as you?
너만큼 좋은 여자를 또 어디서 찾을 수 있겠어?
And my mom too...
그리고 우리 엄마도...
I'm jealous. Your family seems so warm.
나는 질투한다. 가족들이 참 따뜻해 보이네요.
Your family is nice,
당신의 가족은 좋은,
but I don't have a father,
하지만 나에겐 아버지가 없다.
and my relationship with my mom is strained.
엄마와의 관계도 긴장됐어요.
Of course, she wouldn't like me.
물론 그녀는 나를 좋아하지 않을 것이다.
Not like you? Who wouldn't?
너 같지 않니? 누가 그러지 않겠습니까?
My mom would never think that way.
우리 엄마는 절대 그렇게 생각하지 않을 거예요.
Don't misunderstand that.
오해하지 마세요.
Besides, in this day and age, divorce happens,
게다가 요즘 같은 시대에는 이혼이 일어나고,
and mothers and daughters argue sometimes.
엄마와 딸은 가끔 논쟁을 벌이기도 합니다.
If anyone says anything about that, bring them to me. I'll teach them a lesson.
누군가 그것에 대해 뭐라고 한다면, 나에게 가져오세요. 나는 그들에게 교훈을 가르칠 것이다.
And
그리고
your mother must have acted out of deep affection.
네 엄마가 꼭 갖고 계실 거야 깊은 애정으로 행동했습니다.
She really cares about you.
그녀는 정말로 당신에게 관심을 갖고 있습니다.
It's just a different way of showing it.
단지 그것을 보여주는 방법이 다를 뿐입니다.
How do you know that, President?
그걸 어떻게 아시나요, 대통령님?
My mom isn't like that at all, okay?
우리 엄마는 전혀 그런 분이 아니잖아요?
What if I'm right about this?
만약 내가 옳다면 어떻게 될까요?
I'm sorry to visit unannounced, but I felt it was the right thing to do.
예고도 없이 방문해서 죄송하고, 하지만 나는 그것이 옳은 일이라고 느꼈습니다.
With all the commotion online,
온라인에서 온갖 소란이 일어나는 가운데,
it's impossible to ignore.
무시하는 것은 불가능합니다.
I sincerely apologize for causing concern.
심려를 끼쳐드려 진심으로 사과드립니다.
I saw it well.
잘 봤습니다.
Thank you
감사합니다
for keeping your word back then.
그때 약속을 지키셨으니까요.
I hope Hui Won
희원이 좋겠다
doesn't live
살지 않는다
like I did.
내가 그랬던 것처럼.
So
그래서
keep that promise.
그 약속을 지키세요.
I'll be watching for now.
지금은 지켜보겠습니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Your mother must have acted out of deep affection.
당신의 어머니가 있어야합니다 깊은 애정으로 행동했습니다.
She really cares about you.
그녀는 정말로 당신에게 관심을 갖고 있습니다.
[Mom]
[엄마]
How was your meeting with your future daughter-in-law?
와의 만남은 어땠나요? 미래의 며느리?
What a shame. Invite me to the formal meeting too.
정말 부끄러운 일입니다. 나를 초대 공식 회의에도.
We're family after all.
결국 우리는 가족이에요.
What brings you here unannounced?
예고도 없이 무슨 일로 여기까지 왔나요?
I believe the time has come.
나는 때가 왔다고 믿는다.
You remember what I said before, right?
제가 전에 한 말 기억하시나요?
Give me Taehan Liquor.
태한주 주세요.
It was supposed to be Han Jun's anyway.
어차피 한준의 것이었겠지.
What if I say no?
내가 거절하면 어떻게 되나요?
You'll see for yourself why you have no choice but to say yes.
왜 당신인지 스스로 알게 될 것이다. 그렇다고 말할 수밖에 없습니다.
Well, it probably wasn't that important a matter.
글쎄, 아마 그렇지 않았을 거야 그 중요한 문제야.
Then I'll tell you again.
그럼 다시 말씀드리겠습니다.
Co-President of Taehan Liquor.
대한주류 공동대표.
Let's start from there.
거기부터 시작합시다.
The murderer who killed his brother for power.
죽인 살인자 권력을 위해 그의 형제.
Du Jun has been through so much because of this, you know.
두준이 너무 고생했어 이 때문에 알잖아요.
But what can I do?
하지만 내가 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
The next heir of Taehan Group
대한그룹 차기 후계자
abused drugs, even psychiatric medication.
약물 남용, 심지어 정신과 약물까지.
What should I do next?
다음에 무엇을 해야 합니까?
Knock it off!
그것을 노크하세요!
Once again, you only think of your son.
다시 한번 당신은 당신의 아들만을 생각합니다.
The trauma from back then can't repeat itself, right?
그때의 트라우마 같은 말을 반복할 수는 없지, 그렇지?
What now, again?
이제 또 어쩌지?
What brings you here?
무슨 일로 여기까지 왔나요?
I guess you haven't heard yet.
아직 들어보시지 못한 것 같아요.
I'm here as the representative of Taehan Liquor.
제가 대표로 왔습니다. 대한주류.
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
As of today, we're co-presidents.
오늘부로 우리는 공동대표입니다.
Let's get along well.
잘 지내자.
What does that mean?
그게 무슨 뜻이에요?
Co-presidents?
공동회장?
The board discussed your dismissal.
이사회에서는 귀하의 해고에 대해 논의했습니다.
Who would entrust a company
누가 회사에 맡길 것인가
to someone relying on drugs to manage it?
그것을 관리하기 위해 약물에 의존하는 사람에게?
They claimed your press conference outburst was due to unmedicated mood swings.
그들은 당신의 기자회견이 폭발했다고 주장했습니다 약물 치료를 받지 않은 기분 변화 때문이었습니다.
That medication was properly prescribed. Who would...
그 약은 제대로 됐어 처방. 누가...
Try saying that in front of the board. Who would believe such a thing?
칠판 앞에서 이렇게 말해 보세요. 누가 그런 말을 믿겠습니까?
I think the time for focusing on the truth has passed.
집중할 때가 된 것 같아요 진실은 지나갔습니다.
The board thinks that recently,
이사회는 최근에 다음과 같이 생각합니다.
your actions are not
당신의 행동은 그렇지 않습니다
those of a company owner.
회사 오너의 것.
So I'll be joining you for a while.
그래서 잠시 동안 여러분과 함께하겠습니다.
I'll attend all meetings and schedules going forward. Be aware.
나는 모든 회의와 일정에 참석할 것이다. 앞으로. 주의하세요.
Then who decided this?
그럼 이건 누가 결정한 걸까요?
- If the Chairman knew... - It was the Chairman's decision.
- 회장님이 아신다면... - 회장님의 결정이었습니다.
You hadn't heard yet?
아직 듣지 못하셨나요?
The communication between father and son is really...
사이의 통신 아버지와 아들은 정말...
Go ask him for the details.
가서 그에게 자세한 내용을 물어보세요.
So,
그래서,
where should I sit?
어디에 앉아야 하나?
Unbelievable!
믿을 수 없는!
Big news! Big news!
빅뉴스! 빅뉴스!
We have a new co-president at our company!
우리 회사에 새로운 공동 사장이 생겼습니다!
Then what about President Kang Du Jun?
그렇다면 강두준 회장은 어떨까?
Rumor has it he's been on psychiatric medication,
소문에 의하면 그 사람은 그랬다고 하네 정신과 약물 치료에 대해,
quite a lot of it.
꽤 많습니다.
The President? Is it fake news?
대통령? 가짜뉴스인가요?
No, because of the trauma, they say daily life is impossible without medication.
아니 트라우마 때문에 그러는데 약물 없이는 일상생활이 불가능하다.
It hasn't even been long since the scandal explanation, and now a drug controversy too.
스캔들 나온지 얼마 안됐는데 설명, 그리고 이제는 마약 논란도 마찬가지입니다.
This might be quite troublesome.
꽤 귀찮은 일이 아닐 수 없습니다.
Right?
오른쪽?
So what will happen to President now?
그렇다면 이제 대통령은 어떻게 될까요?
Is he getting kicked out?
그 사람 쫓겨나는 거야?
Huh?
뭐?
That's ridiculous.
말도 안 돼요.
That can't be true.
그것은 사실일 수 없습니다.
How would you know whether it makes sense or not?
어떻게 알겠어요? 그게 말이 되는지 안 되는지?
Like last time, do you know anything about this?
지난번처럼 아시죠? 이것에 대해 아무것도?
- That's not it. - It's not even verified information yet.
- 그게 아니야. - 아직 확인된 정보도 아닙니다.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
성급하게 결론을 내리지 맙시다.
The rumors could be distorted, like with the previous scandal.
소문이 왜곡될 수도 있고, 이전 스캔들처럼요.
Let's just trust him and wait.
그냥 그를 믿고 기다리자.
Yeah, our president would never.
응, 우리 대통령은 절대 안 그럴 거야.
Oh, no way.
아, 절대 안돼.
Hey, tell them not to spread weird rumors.
야, 이상한 소문 퍼뜨리지 말라고 해.
We have enough to worry about already.
우리는 이미 걱정할 만큼 충분합니다.
Anyway, this needs to be precise.
아무튼 정확해야 합니다.
After that day, whenever someone touched my hand, even slightly,
그 날 이후에는 누군가가 언제라도 손으로 살짝만 만져도
my body would freeze automatically.
내 몸은 자동으로 얼어붙을 것이다.
Is it because of his hands?
손 때문인가요?
[Market share trends by sales channel]
[판매채널별 시장점유율 추이]
[Risk flag for sales share trends by channel] Convenience store channel share dropped
[채널별 매출 비중 동향 리스크 플래그] 편의점 채널 점유율 하락
from 23% last year to 19% this year.
지난해 23%에서 올해 19%로 늘었다.
A four percent drop is pretty serious, isn't it?
4% 하락 꽤 심각하지 않나요?
Instead, big mart share rose by 3.8%.
대신 대형마트 점유율은 3.8% 상승했다.
The margin here is much higher.
여기서 마진은 훨씬 더 높습니다.
For export volumes here, the Southeast Asia margin rate is 12%.
수출량의 경우, 동남아시아 마진율은 12%입니다.
After shipping costs, is there any profit left?
배송비 후, 이익이 남아있나요?
You may not get it yet, but Southeast Asia prioritizes market share capture.
아직 이해가 안 되실 수도 있겠지만, 동남아 시장 점유율 확보를 최우선으로 생각합니다.
How long will you focus solely on market share?
언제까지 집중할 것인가 시장점유율로만?
Last month's sales fulfillment rate was halved.
지난달 판매 이행률이 절반으로 줄었습니다.
When you ran the hotel, President Han,
한 대표님이 호텔을 운영하실 때,
even if you lowered margins off-season, wasn't room occupancy your priority?
비수기 마진을 낮추더라도 방 점유가 우선순위 아니었나요?
The liquor industry is no different.
주류업계도 다르지 않다.
Shouldn't we consider the entire industry is in a recession?
우리가 고려하면 안 될까? 업계 전체가 불황?
Interesting.
흥미로운.
Speaking of which, there's an ongoing in-house contest.
말하자면, 사내 공모전이 진행 중이에요.
How's that progressing?
어떻게 진행되고 있나요?
Ah, yes.
아, 그렇죠.
Following Try Beer,
Try Beer에 이어,
we decided to actively incorporate ideas from all employees
적극적으로 도입하기로 결정했습니다. 전 직원의 아이디어
to create the next flagship beer for Taehan Liquor.
차세대 플래그십 맥주를 만들기 위해 대한주류.
And we're actually awarding cash prizes.
그리고 우리는 실제로 상금을 수여하고 있습니다.
[Finding the Next Try Beer] We're even considering launching
[다음 맥주를 찾아라] 출시도 고려하고 있어요
the first-place winner's idea as a product,
1등 수상자의 아이디어를 제품으로,
so I hear the employees are preparing diligently.
그래서 직원들의 말을 듣고 열심히 준비하고 있습니다.
[Award details] Well, the prize money seems stingy for that.
[수상내역] 글쎄, 그러기엔 상금이 아깝나 보다.
We should triple the prize money
상금을 3배로 늘려야지
and most importantly, instead of keeping this internal,
그리고 가장 중요한 것은 대신에 이것을 내부적으로 유지하고,
we need to promote it widely,
널리 홍보해야죠
so consumers can get excited too.
그래서 소비자도 흥분할 수 있어요.
When the winning product launches, let everyone try it themselves.
당첨된 제품이 출시되면, 모두가 스스로 시도해 보도록 하세요.
What do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
What's this? Domestic hop ale beer?
이건 뭐죠? 국산 홉에일 맥주?
[Domestic hop ale beer] Yes, that's our team's new product.
[국산 홉에일맥주] 네, 그게 우리 팀의 신제품이에요.
Domestic hops?
국산 홉?
Interesting.
흥미로운.
What's the production cost?
생산 비용은 얼마입니까?
- Well, the cost... - It's still in testing phase.
- 음, 비용이... - 아직 테스트 단계입니다.
That makes cost control even more critical.
이는 비용 통제를 더욱 중요하게 만듭니다.
Without cost management, even the best idea is useless.
비용관리 없이, 아무리 좋은 아이디어라도 쓸모가 없습니다.
Let's call the person in charge.
담당자에게 전화하자.
- Pardon? - Why do we need the person in charge here?
- 뭐라고요? - 여기에 담당자가 왜 필요한가요?
If you're curious, ask me.
궁금하시다면 저에게 물어보세요.
Why?
왜?
Is there a reason I can't call them directly?
직접 전화할 수 없는 이유가 있나요?
The concept is refreshing from the start.
컨셉부터 참신하네요.
And it has market potential.
그리고 시장 잠재력이 있습니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
I'm curious about the proper way to drink and appreciate it.
적절한 방법이 궁금합니다 마시고 감사합니다.
Can you demonstrate it?
그것을 보여주실 수 있나요?
From pouring into the glass to tasting.
잔에 따르는 것부터 시음까지.
Why must it be done during the meeting?
왜 회의 중에 해야 합니까?
Ask me after the meeting is over.
회의가 끝나면 나에게 물어보세요.
It'll be quick,
빨리 될 거예요,
and the person in charge is already here.
그리고 담당자는 이미 와있습니다.
I'm inexperienced in this,
저는 이 분야에 경험이 없습니다.
so I wanted to see how to pour and taste it properly to enjoy the flavor.
그래서 어떻게 붓는지 보고 싶었어요 맛을 제대로 즐기려면 제대로 맛보세요.
If she directly handled the product,
그녀가 직접 제품을 취급했다면,
it must be different, right?
분명 다를 거에요, 그렇죠?
I apologize.
사과드립니다.
Actually, I'm currently...
사실 저는 지금...
Are you joking right now?
지금 농담하는 겁니까?
Manager Jang, didn't you know the prototype had quality issues
장과장님, 프로토타입을 모르셨나요? 품질 문제가 있었습니다
so we scrapped the entire batch?
그래서 우리가 전체 배치를 폐기했나요?
I'm sorry, but I received a late report that the hop farm had financial issues,
죄송합니다만 늦게 보고를 받았습니다 홉 농장에 재정적인 문제가 있었다는 걸요.
which affected the prototype quality.
이는 프로토타입 품질에 영향을 미쳤습니다.
I'll report to you as soon as the redeveloped prototype is ready.
일단 보고할게 재개발된 프로토타입이 준비되었습니다.
It's my fault. I sincerely apologize.
내 잘못이야. 진심으로 사과드립니다.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
So you are really pregnant?
그럼 정말 임신한 건가요?
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you earlier.
미리 말씀드리지 못해 죄송합니다.
But I did my utmost not to affect the project.
하지만 난 최선을 다했어 프로젝트에 영향을 미치지 않도록 합니다.
I never neglected my duties
나는 한 번도 내 의무를 소홀히 한 적이 없다.
due to pregnancy, not even once.
임신으로 인해 단 한 번도.
So?
그래서?
I'll step down if I must.
필요하다면 물러나겠습니다.
I'll prepare the handover.
인계를 준비하겠습니다.
You're the one in charge, aren't you?
당신이 책임자죠, 그렇죠?
Pardon?
뭐라고요?
So you have to take responsibility until the very end.
그러니까 책임을 져야지 끝까지.
Keep going as far as you can.
가능한 한 계속 가십시오.
Whether it's tasting or condition issues,
맛 문제든 상태 문제든,
get help from the team.
팀의 도움을 받으세요.
Just because you're pregnant doesn't mean you can't work.
단지 임신했다는 이유만으로 일을 할 수 없다는 뜻은 아니다.
Don't be stubborn,
고집 부리지 말고,
trying to do everything alone.
모든 일을 혼자 하려고 합니다.
Team Leader.
팀 리더.
Why did you help me earlier?
아까 왜 나를 도와줬어요?
You don't even like me, Team Leader.
당신은 나를 좋아하지도 않는군요, 팀 리더.
Do I not?
나는 그렇지 않습니까?
Well, you're my junior at work.
글쎄, 당신은 직장에서 내 후배야.
What?
무엇?
I'm the only one who can scold you.
당신을 꾸짖을 수 있는 사람은 나뿐이에요.
- Team Leader. - Get out.
- 팀 리더. - 나가세요.
I explicitly told you not to mess with her.
나는 분명히 그녀를 건드리지 말라고 말했습니다.
I've tolerated you this far out of respect for my brother, but I have my limits.
존경하는 마음으로 지금까지 참아왔습니다 하지만 나에게는 한계가 있다.
Do you think I came here just for you?
내가 단지 당신을 위해 여기에 왔다고 생각합니까?
What do you mean by that?
그게 무슨 뜻이에요?
Manager Jang is quite capable, you know.
장과장님은 꽤 유능하시죠.
It's a shame that such talent is overshadowed by you.
이런 재능이 있다는 게 안타깝다. 당신에 의해 가려졌습니다.
Please just stay still.
그냥 가만히 있어주세요.
If you'd just stay put,
그냥 가만히 있었으면
I plan to give opportunities to the capable Manager Jang to shine.
기회를 줄 생각이다 유능한 장감독이 빛날 수 있도록.
But if you try to do something,
하지만 뭔가를 하려고 하면,
I'll bet everything to block Manager Jang's path.
막는 데 모든 걸 걸겠어 장 감독의 길.
I'll do it if I decide to.
내가 결정하면 그렇게 할게요.
You know that, right?
그거 알지?
Then give it your best shot.
그런 다음 최선을 다해 노력하십시오.
I'll also do whatever it takes this time
나도 이번에는 뭐든지 할게
to stop you, no matter what.
무슨 일이 있어도 당신을 막기 위해.
Father!
아버지!
What on earth is going on?
도대체 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
Did something happen with Jeong Eum?
정음한테 무슨 일이라도 생긴 걸까?
Looks like Moo Young and she are really set on playing this game.
무영이랑 닮음 정말 이 게임을 플레이할 준비가 되어있습니다.
They've swayed the entire board to their side,
그들은 흔들렸다 보드 전체를 자기 쪽으로,
so there was nothing I could do immediately.
그래서 당장 할 수 있는 일은 아무것도 없었다.
We don't need executives who only care about their own interests.
우리는 단지 경영진이 필요하지 않습니다 자신의 이익에 관심을 갖습니다.
We should just take them all down at once.
한꺼번에 다 쓰러뜨려야 합니다.
You know better than anyone that's not the point.
누구보다도 당신이 잘 알고 있어요 그게 요점이 아닙니다.
To overcome this situation,
이러한 상황을 극복하기 위해,
you must conquer it yourself.
스스로 이겨내야 합니다.
Otherwise that trauma
그렇지 않으면 그 트라우마
will trip you up at another critical moment.
또 다른 중요한 순간에 당신을 넘어지게 할 것입니다.
Now it's your turn to show them.
이제 당신이 보여줄 차례입니다.
That this won't break you,
이것이 당신을 망치지 않을 것입니다.
that you can stand strong without the medication.
네가 굳건히 설 수 있다는 걸 약 없이.
Focus on proving it yourself.
스스로 증명하는 데 집중하세요.
I'll look into the board issue myself.
보드 문제는 제가 직접 조사해보겠습니다.
Understood?
이해했다?
Yes.
예.
Now it's your turn to show them.
이제 당신이 보여줄 차례입니다.
That this won't break you,
이것이 당신을 망치지 않을 것입니다.
that you can stand strong without the medication.
네가 굳건히 설 수 있다는 걸 약 없이.
Focus on proving it yourself.
스스로 증명하는 데 집중하세요.
President.
대통령.
What's on your mind?
무슨 생각을 하고 있나요?
Nothing. You were really startled earlier, weren't you?
아무것도 아님. 당신은 정말로 좀 전에 깜짝 놀랐지, 그렇지?
I should have stopped it beforehand.
미리 막았어야 했는데.
Is this the time to worry about me?
지금이 나를 걱정할 때인가?
I know exactly what kind of person she is.
나는 그녀가 어떤 사람인지 정확히 알고 있습니다.
Will you really be okay?
정말 괜찮을까요?
Co-presidents? Seriously?
공동회장? 진지하게?
I'm already preparing countermeasures.
이미 대책을 준비하고 있어요.
I won't just sit back and take it this time, so don't worry too much.
이번에는 그냥 가만히 앉아만 있지는 않을 거예요. 그러니 너무 걱정하지 마세요.
I'll help too.
나도 도와줄게.
Just tell me what to do.
무엇을 해야할지 말해 주세요.
Leave this to me.
이건 나에게 맡겨주세요.
Hui Won, just stay by my side as you are now.
희원아, 지금처럼만 내 옆에 있어줘.
That's enough for me.
나는 그것으로 충분합니다.
The subscriber you are calling is not available.
전화를 걸고 있는 가입자 사용할 수 없습니다.
- Mom, seriously. - Please leave a message...
- 엄마, 정말요. - 메시지를 남겨주세요...
[Mom]
[엄마]
The subscriber you are calling is not available.
전화를 걸고 있는 가입자 사용할 수 없습니다.
Oh my. What's going on?
아, 이런. 무슨 일이야?
What were you even thinking?
대체 무슨 생각을 하고 있었던 걸까?
Mom.
엄마.
It's the board's decision.
이사회의 결정입니다.
Is there any reason to refuse?
거절할 이유가 있나요?
That makes no sense.
그건 말도 안 돼요.
Uncle isn't taking weird drugs or anything.
삼촌은 이상한 약이나 그런 것을 복용하지 않습니다.
Why is the company pushing him like this?
회사는 왜 그를 이렇게 밀어붙이는 걸까?
Are you really going as far as proposing his dismissal?
정말 여기까지 가시나요? 해고를 제안한다고요?
It was your dad's anyway.
어쨌든 그건 네 아버지의 것이었어.
He would've passed Taehan Liquor to you.
그 사람은 당신에게 대한주를 건네줬을 거예요.
So it was you, Mom.
그래서 당신이었어요, 엄마.
You were behind it all.
모든 일의 배후에는 당신이 있었습니다.
If you feel wronged, participate in the voting.
당신이 부당하다고 느끼면, 투표에 참여합니다.
If you want to use your voting rights.
의결권을 행사하고 싶은 경우.
How could you? You know about my relationship with Uncle.
어떻게 그럴 수 있니? 알잖아 나와 삼촌의 관계에 대해.
Your uncle is the one who made you lose your father.
당신의 삼촌이 그 사람입니다 아버지를 잃게 만든 사람.
He's the one who destroyed our family.
그 사람은 우리 가족을 파괴한 사람이에요.
You think he'll still look out for you once he has his own real family?
그 사람이 아직도 당신을 돌봐줄 거라고 생각하는 걸까요? 그에게 진짜 가족이 생기면?
Make your choice.
선택하세요.
Me or your uncle?
나 아니면 네 삼촌?
That's ridiculous.
말도 안 돼요.
What do I even have left?
나한테 남은 게 도대체 뭐지?
For me,
나에게는
you're all I've got now.
당신은 지금 내가 가진 전부입니다.
In other words,
즉,
since the drug scandal involving President Kang Du Jun has erupted,
마약 스캔들 이후 강두준 회장이 터졌다.
our board has concluded saving the situation is no longer possible.
우리 이사회는 결론을 내렸습니다 상황을 저장하는 것은 더 이상 불가능합니다.
I can't accept this.
나는 이것을 받아들일 수 없다.
Using someone's private medical records like this?
다른 사람의 개인 정보를 사용하여 이런 진료기록?
The President's health isn't a private matter.
대통령의 건강 사적인 문제가 아닙니다.
It directly impacts the company's management.
이는 회사 경영에 직접적인 영향을 미칩니다.
I even doubt whether the decisions made so far were based on sound judgment.
결정이 맞는지조차 의심스럽습니다 지금까지의 판단은 건전한 판단을 바탕으로 이루어졌습니다.
I've performed my duties with a sound mind, and my track record proves it.
나는 건전한 정신으로 임무를 수행해왔고, 내 실적이 그것을 증명합니다.
Would someone like that commit such impulsive acts?
누군가 그런 걸 좋아할까? 그런 충동적인 행동을 저질렀나요?
You can't even manage a simple handshake at official events.
간단한 관리조차 할 수 없습니다. 공식 행사에서 악수.
Isn't the fact that you haven't overcome that handshake trauma
당신이하지 않았다는 사실이 아닙니까? 악수 트라우마를 극복하다
already a sign of insufficient leadership qualities?
이미 부족하다는 신호 리더십 자질?
For a businessperson, a handshake signifies trust.
사업가의 경우, 악수는 신뢰를 의미합니다.
Is it acceptable to fail to build even that much trust?
실패하는 것이 용납될 수 있는가 그렇게까지 신뢰를 쌓으려고?
That's true.
그것은 사실이다.
Makes sense, he can't even do that.
말이 되는군요. 그는 심지어 그렇게도 할 수 없습니다.
Why not step down voluntarily at this point?
현 시점에서 자발적으로 물러나는 것은 어떨까요?
Rumors are widespread that you hold the position by bloodline, not merit.
당신이 가지고 있다는 소문이 널리 퍼졌습니다. 장점이 아닌 혈통에 따른 위치.
At least do it if there's any conscience left.
최소한 해라 양심이 조금이라도 남아있다면.
Let's just start voting right now.
지금 바로 투표를 시작해 볼까요?
Exactly. What's the point of delaying?
정확히. 지체하면 무슨 소용이 있나요?
The result will be the same anyway.
결과는 어차피 마찬가지일 것이다.
- Fine. - Let's vote right now.
- 괜찮은. - 지금 당장 투표합시다.
- Let's vote. - Come on.
- 투표합시다. - 어서 해봐요.
Well, if that's how everyone feels,
뭐, 다들 그렇게 생각한다면,
we'll proceed with the vote now...
이제 투표를 진행하겠습니다...
Board matters must be notified at least a week in advance.
이사회 사항을 통보해야 함 적어도 일주일 전에.
I surely mentioned it on the day I came to work.
분명 언급했는데 출근하던 날.
That your dismissal would soon be discussed at the board meeting.
곧 해고될 거라고 이사회에서 논의할 것.
Is a casual remark in the office considered legal notice?
사무실에서 아무렇지도 않은 발언이다 법적 고지로 간주됩니까?
Decisions made by a board meeting with stakeholders directly involved
이사회에서 결정 이해관계자가 직접 참여하는
may have legal issues.
법적인 문제가 있을 수 있습니다.
If you insist on voting today,
오늘 투표를 고집한다면,
I will hold every single person here accountable.
한 사람 한 사람 다 내가 안아줄게 여기에 책임이 있습니다.
Do you
당신은
still wish to proceed?
아직도 계속하시겠습니까?
So what exactly are you trying to say?
그렇다면 정확히 무엇을 말하려는 걸까요?
Give me two weeks.
2주만 주세요.
I'm asking for the chance to explain myself through proper procedures.
나 자신에 대해 설명할 기회를 달라는 거야 적절한 절차를 거쳐
It's not too late
너무 늦진 않았어
to vote then.
그럼 투표하러.
Does he really think he can get anything done in two weeks?
그 사람은 정말로 자신이 얻을 수 있다고 생각하는 걸까요? 2주 안에 뭐 한 거야?
Not a chance.
기회가 아닙니다.
What's in it for you joining forces with her?
당신이 그녀와 힘을 합치게 된 이유는 무엇입니까?
What's this all of a sudden?
갑자기 이게 무슨 소리야?
Do you really think she will stand with you until the end?
정말로 그녀가 그럴 거라고 생각하시나요? 끝까지 함께 있어줄래?
Don't even think about provoking me.
나를 자극할 생각은 하지도 마세요.
It's a waste of time anyway.
어쨌든 시간 낭비입니다.
The incident fifteen years ago, you remember it, right?
15년 전 사건, 기억나지?
Those of you who helped turn me into a murderer back then.
나를 변화시키는 데 도움을 주신 분들 그땐 살인자로 변했어.
The journalists you were close with then are now all department heads or deputy heads.
그때 친하게 지냈던 기자들 이제 모두 부서장 또는 부국장입니다.
It's all in the past. What can you possibly do?
그것은 모두 과거의 일입니다. 당신은 무엇을 할 수 있습니까?
True. Unfortunately, there's no evidence for that case.
진실. 안타깝게도 없습니다. 그 사건의 증거.
Then how about this?
그럼 이건 어때요?
You've been manipulating the financial statements little by little for 11 years.
당신은 금융을 조작하고 있습니다 11년 동안 조금씩 진술을 해왔다.
Do you really think I don't know where all that slush fund money went?
내가 정말 모른다고 생각하시나요? 그 비자금은 다 어디로 갔나요?
Fortunately, I haven't told Father yet.
다행스럽게도 나는 아직 아버지께 말씀드리지 않았습니다.
But he'll find out soon enough.
하지만 그는 곧 알게 될 것이다.
Wait a minute.
잠깐 기다려요.
Let me think for a moment...
잠시 생각해보자...
I'm giving you an opportunity right now.
지금 바로 여러분에게 기회를 드리고 있습니다.
Cut ties with her and persuade the board.
그녀와의 관계를 끊고 이사회를 설득하세요.
If it goes to prosecution, you are finished too.
검찰로 가면, 너도 끝났어.
You understand that, right?
이해하시죠?
No, wait...
아니, 잠깐...
So, how was it?
그래서 어땠나요?
Did it hit the mark?
목표에 도달했나요?
Seems like he roughly understood.
대충 이해한 것 같습니다.
So what are you going to do now?
그럼 이제 무엇을 할 건가요?
I'm going to stick with the plan.
나는 그 계획을 고수할 것이다.
I've thrown out the bait, so something will bite.
미끼를 던져버렸어요 그래서 뭔가 물릴 것입니다.
When are you going to reveal the evidence?
증거는 언제 공개할 겁니까?
When the time is right.
때가되면.
Not yet. I need to save it.
아직 아님. 저장해야 해요.
Whew, my heart's pounding.
휴, 심장이 쿵쾅거린다.
By the way, shouldn't you tell Ms. Hui Won about today's board meeting?
그런데, 말해야 하지 않나? 원희씨 오늘 이사회에 대해서요?
She needs to know your situation right now.
그녀는 지금 당신의 상황을 알아야 합니다.
Keep it a secret from Hui Won.
희원에게는 비밀로 해주세요.
Why?
왜?
She's with child. I'm sure it's tough for her.
그녀는 아이를 갖고 있어요. 나는 그것이 그녀에게 힘든 일이라고 확신합니다.
I want to stop making her worry.
나는 그녀를 걱정하게 만드는 것을 멈추고 싶습니다.
But...
하지만...
Tak Soo.
탁수.
[Packaging, Campaign Slogan] I asked for those images earlier.
[포장, 캠페인 슬로건] 아까 그 이미지를 요청했어요.
[Market Analysis] Give me those images.
[시장분석] 그 이미지를 주세요.
Ah, it's right here.
아, 바로 여기군요.
Send those over quickly.
빨리 보내주세요.
[Target & Branding Strategy] Sent.
[타겟 및 브랜딩 전략] 보냈습니다.
Assistant Manager Choi, please just go home.
최 대리님, 그냥 집에 가세요.
[Revenue Projections, Distribution Strategy] Jeez.
[수익전망, 배분전략] 이런.
Check the bottom part.
하단 부분을 확인해보세요.
The prize money tripling is great news,
상금이 3배로 늘어난 소식이군요.
but isn't it unfair that we can't submit as a team?
하지만 그건 불공평하지 않아? 팀으로 제출할 수는 없나요?
Still, it's such a relief that everyone's developing their own stuff.
그래도 너무 다행이다. 모두가 자신만의 것을 개발하고 있어요.
I'm almost done.
이제 거의 끝났습니다.
Let me know if you need help.
도움이 필요하면 알려주세요.
Manager Jang, help me out.
장과장님, 도와주세요.
Look at this. Fix this part.
이것 좀 보세요. 이 부분을 수정하세요.
[Upload Complete] Even if I fix this, it still doesn't work.
[업로드 완료] 이걸 고쳐도 여전히 안되네요.
Assistant Manager Choi, please go home.
최 대리님 집에 가세요.
- Se Hyeon, do you need anything? - I'm just so worried.
- 세현아, 뭐 필요한 거 없어? - 정말 걱정이 돼요.
Tak Soo, I told you to send me that earlier.
탁수야, 아까 그거 보내라고 했잖아.
It's okay. You always look out for me and help me.
괜찮아요. 넌 항상 조심해 나를 위해 도와주세요.
- I'll handle it myself. - That's why I asked.
- 제가 직접 처리하겠습니다. -그래서 물었습니다.
- Oh, yeah? - It's not my fault, okay?
- 아, 그래요? - 내 잘못은 아니잖아, 알았지?
- But if you need anything, just say it. - You just go home!
- 하지만 필요한 것이 있으면 말씀하세요. - 그냥 집에 가세요!
Yes, thank you.
네, 감사합니다.
Why? What's wrong?
왜? 무슨 일이야?
Huh? What's happening?
뭐? 무슨 일이야?
Why did it suddenly stop?
왜 갑자기 멈췄나요?
Jeez, get a grip.
이런, 꽉 잡아.
Seeing this, I think we're the real winners for giving up early.
이걸 보니 우리는 일찍 포기한 진정한 승자.
Right? But seeing them prepare for the contest while so busy,
오른쪽? 그런데 준비하는 걸 보니 바쁜 와중에도 대회 때문에
they're all amazing.
그들은 모두 놀랍습니다.
I admit that.
나는 그것을 인정한다.
What's wrong? What!
무슨 일이야? 무엇!
Yes! It's working again!
예! 다시 작동합니다!
Jeez.
이런.
[Target & Branding Strategy] No typos...
[타겟 및 브랜딩 전략] 오타가 없습니다...
Save.
저장합니다.
[Upload Complete] All done.
[업로드 완료] 모두 완료되었습니다.
- Submission complete. - I'm exhausted.
- 제출이 완료되었습니다. - 지쳤어요.
I feel like I did all of this.
이 모든 것을 내가 한 것 같은 느낌이 듭니다.
[Upload Complete] Look at me sweating.
[업로드 완료] 땀 흘리는 나를 보세요.
I'm done too.
나도 끝났어.
Alright then.
그럼요.
The contest is over now.
이제 대회가 끝났습니다.
- Let's have pork belly after work! - I'm in!
- 퇴근하고 삼겹살 먹자! - 내가 들어갈게!
I have to bathe the kids today.
오늘은 아이들을 목욕시켜야 해요.
Then Manager Nah will pass. What about the rest?
그러면 나 감독은 합격할 것이다. 나머지는 어떻습니까?
Assistant Manager Choi! Skipping me just like that?
최 대리! 그렇게 날 건너뛰는 거야?
I'll go. Everyone else is okay with it, right?
나는 갈 것이다. 다른 사람들 괜찮아요?
Ah, I have plans today.
아, 오늘은 계획이 있어요.
- I'm sorry. - Come on.
- 죄송합니다. - 어서 해봐요.
Ah, why?
아, 왜요?
I've been pushing myself too hard lately, so I'm not feeling well.
나 자신을 너무 몰아붙였어 최근에 몸이 안 좋아서요.
Ah, really?
아, 정말요?
When your condition is off, one shot of soju will wipe the fatigue.
컨디션이 안 좋을 때, 소주 한잔이면 피로가 풀립니다.
Why are you pressuring someone who's unwell to drink?
왜 압박하는 거야? 몸이 안좋아서 술 못 마시는 사람?
I didn't force it, but I'm just disappointed.
강요하진 않았지만 그냥 실망스럽네요.
I know, she must be the most disappointed.
나도 알아요, 그녀가 가장 실망했을 거에요.
Why are you feeling disappointed on her behalf?
왜 기분이 좋지? 그녀 대신에 실망했나요?
If anyone in our team forces alcohol, you'll get a serious scolding from me.
우리 팀원 중 누군가가 술을 강요한다면, 당신은 나에게 심각한 질책을 받게 될 것입니다.
Got it?
알았어요?
Yes.
예.
What's gotten into Team Leader?
팀 리더에는 무엇이 들어있나요?
Taking Manager Jang's side completely?
장과장 편을 완전히 들어주는 건가요?
Exactly.
정확히.
When did I ever force anyone?
내가 언제 누군가에게 강요한 적이 있었나요?
The leader does the forcing daily!
리더는 매일 강요를 한다!
I can hear everything.
나는 모든 것을들을 수 있습니다.
What should we eat?
우리는 무엇을 먹어야 합니까?
Let's have pork belly.
삼겹살을 먹자.
I know a place.
나는 한 곳을 알고 있다.
There's a great spot nearby. It's newly opened, and it's amazing.
근처에 좋은 곳이 있어요. 새로 오픈했는데, 정말 놀랍습니다.
Nice.
멋진.
Doors closing.
문이 닫힙니다.
By the way, I apologize for last time.
그런데 지난번에는 사과드립니다.
I momentarily forgot you were pregnant.
나는 당신이 임신했다는 사실을 잠시 잊었습니다.
It's okay.
괜찮아요.
You're not happy I came, are you?
내가 와서 기쁘지 않죠?
You wonder if I'm scheming again around him, right?
내가 또 음모를 꾸미고 있는 게 아닐까 궁금해지나요? 그 사람 주변에 있지, 그렇지?
I can't say I don't.
나는 그렇지 않다고 말할 수 없다.
I'm not someone who mixes personal feelings into work.
나는 섞는 사람이 아니다. 개인적인 감정을 업무에 적용합니다.
When I look at you, it's like seeing my old self.
내가 당신을 볼 때, 마치 나의 옛 모습을 보는 것 같아요.
That's why I feel more invested, perhaps.
그렇기 때문에 아마도 더 많은 투자를 받은 것 같습니다.
Especially after reviewing the projects you handled recently.
특히 검토 후 최근에 처리한 프로젝트.
Honestly, I see you in a new light.
솔직히, 나는 당신을 새로운 시각으로 봅니다.
I want to properly support you going forward.
앞으로도 제대로 지원하고 싶습니다.
- What do you mean? - Just tell me what you want.
- 무슨 뜻이에요? - 원하는 게 무엇인지 말해 보세요.
I can support you with anything.
나는 무엇이든 당신을 지원할 수 있습니다.
Your dream.
당신의 꿈.
I can make it come true.
나는 그것을 실현할 수 있습니다.
No, you don't need to do that.
아니요, 그렇게 할 필요는 없습니다.
I've done well
나는 잘했다
on my own so far.
지금까지 혼자서.
And my dream
그리고 내 꿈
wouldn't mean anything if someone forced it to happen.
아무 의미도 없을 거야 누군가가 강제로 그런 일을 하게 했다면.
Doors opening.
문이 열립니다.
Thank you for the offer, though.
그래도 제안해주셔서 감사합니다.
Then...
그럼...
Is it true our company president went to yours?
사실인가요 우리 회사 사장님 네 집에 갔어?
But didn't you say she is your president's sister-in-law?
하지만 그녀가 그렇다고 말하지 않았나요? 대통령의 처제요?
What is this? It's not even a sibling rivalry. Is it a family feud?
이게 뭔가요? 그것도 아니지 형제간의 경쟁. 가족 불화인가요?
It just made the company atmosphere awkward.
회사 분위기가 어색해지기만 하더군요.
Ugh, this is making me dizzy.
아, 이거 때문에 현기증이 나네요.
So where are you now?
그럼 당신은 지금 어디에 있나요?
Me? On my way home.
나? 집으로 가는 길.
Huh? Let's get food.
뭐? 음식을 구하자.
I'm heading home now too.
나도 지금 집에 가는 중이야.
Now? I want to rest a bit today.
지금? 오늘은 좀 쉬고 싶어요.
Huh?
뭐?
Min Uk is probably waiting by now.
민욱이는 지금쯤 기다리고 있을 것 같다.
- Well...
- 음...
- You go first. - No.
- 먼저 가세요. - 아니.
You go first.
당신이 먼저 가세요.
Mine's not a big deal.
내 것은 큰 문제가 아닙니다.
How's the President doing lately?
최근 대통령님은 잘 지내시나요?
Strange rumors are going around the company.
회사에는 이상한 소문이 돌고 있다.
I heard before he was suffering from something like insomnia.
그 사람이 괴로워하기 전에 들었어 불면증 같은 것에서.
It seems he's still
그 사람은 아직인 것 같아
being misunderstood because of it.
그것 때문에 오해를 받는 거죠.
But I'm not sure.
하지만 잘 모르겠습니다.
He doesn't tell me the details.
그는 나에게 세부 사항을 말하지 않습니다.
I guess he's worried you might worry.
그 사람은 당신이 걱정할까봐 걱정하는 것 같아요.
I can guess what's troubling him,
그 사람을 괴롭히는 것이 무엇인지 추측할 수 있어요.
but I can't solve it for him right now.
하지만 지금 당장은 그 문제를 해결할 수 없어요.
That makes me feel a bit sorry and sad.
그래서 좀 아쉽고 안타깝습니다.
Yeah, this is exactly Jang Hui Won.
네, 바로 장희원입니다.
You stand up for others' problems like they're your own.
당신은 다른 사람의 문제를 옹호합니다. 마치 자기 것인 것처럼.
That's always been your admirable quality.
그것은 항상 당신의 훌륭한 품질이었습니다.
But I think I was too focused on myself.
그런데 제가 너무 제 자신에게만 집중했던 것 같아요.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
- Hey. - So don't worry about it.
- 여기요. - 그러니 걱정하지 마세요.
With our bond this strong, no storm can shake us, right?
우리의 유대가 이렇게 강해서, 어떤 폭풍도 우리를 흔들 수는 없지, 그렇지?
Still,
아직도,
tell me if you need help.
도움이 필요하면 말해주세요.
I'll always be on your side.
나는 항상 당신 편이 될 것입니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Let's go. Mi Ran must be waiting.
갑시다. 미란이 기다리고 있을 거에요.
Yeah.
응.
Are you available for a quick call?
빠른 통화가 가능합니까?
The dismissal proposal?
해고 제안?
Yes, Du Jun told me not to tell you.
네, 두준이한테 말하지 말라고 했어요
But I felt you needed to know, Ms. Hui Won.
하지만 희원씨, 당신이 알아야 할 필요가 있다고 느꼈습니다.
Ah.
아.
Since you're the most important person to Du Jun right now.
당신이 가장 중요하기 때문에 지금 당장 두준에게 사람을 보내세요.
If you're by his side,
당신이 그 사람 옆에 있다면,
he might feel comfortable enough to unburden himself.
그 사람이 편할 수도 있겠지 자신의 부담을 덜어주기에 충분합니다.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
What's going on with the President?
대통령에게 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
There seems to be internal complications.
내부적인 문제가 있는 것 같습니다.
I want to help the President,
나는 대통령을 돕고 싶다.
but I don't know how.
하지만 어떻게 해야 할지 모르겠어요.
I heard at the company
회사에서 들었는데
that the President can't shake hands.
대통령이 악수를 할 수 없다는 것입니다.
Could it be because of that?
그것 때문이 아닐까?
Shake hands?
악수?
Oh, a psychological issue?
아, 심리적인 문제인가요?
How about therapy together?
함께 치료해보시는 건 어떠세요?
He already goes to therapy, I believe.
내 생각엔 그는 이미 치료를 받고 있는 것 같아요.
But I don't mean anything fancy.
그러나 나는 멋진 것을 의미하지 않습니다.
Just having a drink with you guys, talking over my worries,
그냥 너희들끼리 술 한잔하는 것만으로도 내 고민에 대해 이야기하고,
and maybe trashing some people a bit
그리고 어쩌면 몇몇 사람들을 좀 망쳐버릴지도 몰라
can make me feel so much better.
내 기분이 훨씬 나아질 수 있어요.
Hey, who knows?
이봐, 누가 알겠어?
If he just spills his thoughts over a drink with you...
그 사람이 그냥 생각을 쏟아낸다면 너랑 한잔...
Oh, right, you can't drink.
아 맞다 술 못마시잖아
What a shame.
정말 부끄러운 일입니다.
Spill his thoughts?
그의 생각을 유출?
I think I should go see him.
내 생각엔 그를 만나러 가야 할 것 같아.
Huh? What?
뭐? 무엇?
What about dessert?
디저트는 어떻습니까?
Sorry, today you guys go without me.
미안, 오늘 너희들은 나 없이 가거라.
I'll contact you later.
나중에 연락할게요.
Uh, well...
어, 음...
Then we'll just have dessert ourselves.
그럼 우리끼리 디저트 먹자.
Let's just eat this and go.
이것만 먹고 가자.
Huh?
뭐?
Didn't you say we were going for dessert earlier?
우리라고 하지 않았나요? 디저트 먹으러 일찍 갈래?
No.
아니요.
I'll just head home early to rest.
그냥 집에 일찍 가서 쉬겠습니다.
About himself, therapy?
자신에 대해, 치료?
[Trauma Treatment]
[트라우마 치료]
[Group Counseling]
[그룹상담]
[Group Therapy]
[그룹치료]
Do I even have the right to do this?
나에게도 이런 일을 할 권리가 있나요?
I haven't solved my own issues yet.
아직 내 문제를 해결하지 못했습니다.
President.
대통령.
What brings you here, Hui Won?
희원씨, 무슨 일로 여기까지 오셨나요?
What a liar.
정말 거짓말쟁이야.
- What? - You didn't mention the dismissal proposal.
- 무엇? - 해고 제안에 대해서는 언급하지 않았는데요.
Didn't tell me what's troubling you.
당신을 괴롭히는 것이 무엇인지 말하지 않았습니다.
And never once asked for my help.
그리고 한 번도 나에게 도움을 요청한 적이 없습니다.
After giving me all that lecture,
나한테 그 강의를 다 해주고 난 뒤,
you keep doing this yourself?
너 혼자 계속 이러고 있어?
I feel hurt.
마음이 아팠어요.
But how did you...
그런데 어떻게...
- That Secretary Go. - Don't you dare blame Secretary Go.
- 고 비서님. - 감히 고 비서를 비난하지 마세요.
It's just
그것은 단지
this is my problem to solve.
이것이 내가 해결해야 할 문제이다.
You seem to think things
당신은 뭔가 생각하는 것 같아요
only have meaning if solved immediately.
즉시 해결되어야만 의미가 있습니다.
But sometimes,
하지만 때로는
just sharing worries has meaning too.
걱정을 나누는 것만으로도 의미가 있습니다.
When I developed the new product,
새로운 제품을 개발했을 때,
I tried crafting recipes and hop blends alone,
레시피를 만들어 보았습니다 홉 블렌드만 사용하면
but my first attempts were always disasters.
하지만 나의 첫 번째 시도는 항상 재앙이었습니다.
Then when we taste-tested with the team and talked it out,
그러다가 맛을 봤을 때 팀원들과 이야기를 나눴고,
I started seeing solutions.
나는 해결책을 보기 시작했습니다.
Not that we found any grand solution,
우리가 거창한 해결책을 찾은 것은 아닙니다.
but
하지만
sharing made the path clearer.
공유로 인해 경로가 더 명확해졌습니다.
So I want to ask,
그래서 묻고 싶습니다.
are you free the day after tomorrow?
내일 모레 시간 있어?
I need you, President.
저는 당신이 필요합니다, 대통령님.
Would this be okay?
이 정도면 괜찮을까요?
Since you talked about Mom last time, I couldn't call her first.
지난번에 엄마 얘기를 했으니 나는 그녀에게 먼저 전화할 수 없었다.
Just thinking about her,
그녀에 대해 생각하는 것만으로도
I feel lost on where to begin.
어디서부터 시작해야 할지 길을 잃은 것 같아요.
But if you're with me,
하지만 당신이 나와 함께라면,
I think I'll find courage.
용기를 얻을 수 있을 것 같아요.
Well done.
잘하셨어요.
Don't worry, I'll stick right by you.
걱정하지 마세요. 제가 바로 옆에 붙어 있을게요.
Let's go.
갑시다.
It's been four years since my daughter has been a shut-in.
4년이 지났어요 내 딸이 문을 닫은 이후로요.
I was even kneeling at the door.
나는 심지어 문 앞에 무릎을 꿇고 있었다.
- I've hated my father my whole life. - But she wouldn't come out.
- 나는 평생 동안 아버지를 미워했습니다. - 그런데 그 사람은 나오지 않더라고요.
- Because he hit me a lot. - Let alone see me.
- 그 사람이 나를 많이 때렸거든요. - 나 하나만 보자.
- When I was a sophomore in college... - When I look at her...
- 대학교 2학년 때.. - 그 사람을 보면...
It's all my fault.
다 내 잘못이에요.
If only he had said that one thing...
그 사람이 한 마디만 말했더라면...
I want to see Ju Won's face.
주원 씨 얼굴이 보고 싶어요.
- I wouldn't have to resent him like this. - I want to hold her hand just once.
- 이렇게까지 원망할 필요는 없었을 텐데. - 한 번만이라도 손을 잡고 싶어요.
Let's give him some time.
그에게 시간을 좀 주자.
Is there anyone else?
다른 사람이 있나요?
Yes, would you like to share?
네, 공유하시겠습니까?
I...
나는...
I have a difficult relationship with my mom.
나는 엄마와 어려운 관계를 가지고 있습니다.
My mom always
우리 엄마는 항상
thought I ruined her life.
내가 그 사람 인생을 망쳤다고 생각했어요.
So she constantly said
그래서 그녀는 끊임없이 말했다.
that it's
그건
all my fault.
다 내 잘못이야.
My life got completely ruined because of you.
너 때문에 내 인생이 완전히 망가졌어.
If it weren't for you, I...
당신이 아니었다면 나는...
If it weren't for you...
당신이 아니었다면...
Giving birth to you was a mistake from the start.
당신을 낳은 것은 처음부터 실수.
My life has been a mess ever since then. Satisfied?
내 인생은 엉망이었어 그 이후로. 만족하는?
You bad girl.
나쁜 여자야.
How can you only think about yourself until the very end?
어떻게 생각만 할 수 있지? 마지막까지 자신에 대해?
You should never have been born.
당신은 태어나지 말았어야 했어요.
But now,
하지만 지금은,
I'm about to become a mom.
나는 곧 엄마가 될 예정이다.
Oh my, congratulations!
아, 축하해요!
Everyone, let's give her a round of applause.
여러분, 그녀에게 박수를 보내주세요.
Congratulations, really.
정말 축하해요.
I always
나는 항상
gave up and avoided dealing with my mom.
포기하고 엄마와의 거래를 피했습니다.
So when I realized I'm becoming a mom,
그래서 내가 엄마가 되었다는 걸 깨달았을 때,
I was really scared at first.
처음에는 정말 무서웠어요.
Afraid I might say
내가 말할까봐 두려워
to my child,
내 아이에게,
'it's all your fault,'
'다 네 잘못이야'
like my mom did.
우리 엄마가 그랬던 것처럼.
But after meeting my baby's dad,
그런데 아이의 아빠를 만나고 나서
who promised to care for and protect me consistently,
누가 보살펴 주기로 약속했는가 꾸준히 나를 보호해 주시고,
I felt this inexplicable confidence.
나는 설명할 수 없는 자신감을 느꼈다.
Thanks to him,
그 덕분에
I want to understand
나는 이해하고 싶다
my mom better.
우리 엄마가 더 좋아.
Because I want to give this child proper love.
주고 싶기 때문에 이 아이는 올바른 사랑이다.
To do that, I need to first...
그러려면 먼저...
With my mom...
엄마랑...
My mom...
우리 엄마...
You want to restore your relationship with your mom, right?
복원하고 싶으신가요? 너희 엄마와의 관계 맞지?
Yes.
예.
That's why I came here.
그래서 내가 여기 온 거야.
You came to the right place, really.
정말 제대로 찾아오셨습니다.
Let's give her a round of applause.
그녀에게 박수를 보내줍시다.
Welcome.
환영.
I'm so happy for you.
정말 기뻐요.
- Thank you. - See you next time.
- 감사합니다. - 다음에 또 만나요.
You did well.
잘했어요.
You did great, really. It couldn't have been easy.
정말 잘했어요. 쉽지 않았을 겁니다.
I learned all this from you, President.
저는 이 모든 것을 대통령님에게서 배웠습니다.
- Huh? - During your press conference that day,
- 뭐? - 그날 기자간담회에서
you calmly shared your story in front of all those people, right?
차분하게 이야기를 나누셨네요 그 많은 사람들 앞에서 그렇죠?
I don't think everything will be resolved with this one attempt.
모든 게 다 될 것 같지는 않아 이번 한번의 시도로 해결되었습니다.
I'm just trying to think of it as the first step.
난 그냥 노력하고 있어요 첫 번째 단계라고 생각하세요.
Shall we go then?
그럼 우리 갈까?
Yes.
예.
Don't let go. Don't give up, please!
놓지 마십시오. 포기하지 마세요!
I don't think everything will be resolved with this one attempt.
모든 게 다 될 것 같지는 않아 이번 한번의 시도로 해결되었습니다.
I'm just trying to think of it as the first step.
난 그냥 노력하고 있어요 첫 번째 단계라고 생각하세요.
You came to work early.
일찍 출근하셨네요.
I got one iced and one hot. Which one do you want?
저는 아이스 하나, 핫 하나를 먹었어요. 어느 것을 원하세요?
What are you doing? My arms are tired.
뭐하세요? 팔이 피곤해요.
I'll enjoy it.
나는 그것을 즐길 것이다.
What's up with him?
그 사람은 무슨 일이야?
But isn't Manager Nah's idea really good this time?
그런데 나 감독의 생각은 아닌가. 이번엔 정말 좋지?
This high-proof beer can definitely win first place!
이 하이 프루프 맥주 반드시 1위를 차지할 수 있습니다!
The three of us worked on it together!
셋이서 함께 작업했어요!
My precious bunnies!
나의 소중한 토끼들!
Just like him, right?
그 사람과 똑같죠?
Oh, wait a minute!
아, 잠깐만요!
Assistant Manager Choi, Assistant Manager Choi!
최 대리, 최 대리!
- Hey, Kim Tak Soo! - Kim Tak Soo!
- 야, 김탁수! - 김탁수!
Oh, I'm sorry.
아, 미안해요.
Oh! The contest results are announced today!
오! 오늘 공모전 결과가 발표되었습니다!
- Focus. - Really?
- 집중하다. - 정말?
[Today's 2 PM awards ceremony] So we're going to the awards ceremony?
[오늘 오후 2시 시상식] 그럼 시상식에 가볼까요?
Aren't they announcing and then having the ceremony?
발표하고 있지 않은가 그리고 시상식을 하는 거야?
Right? Why did it change again?
오른쪽? 왜 또 바뀌었나요?
Maybe they're planning to give me first place today.
어쩌면 그들은 계획하고 있을지도 모릅니다 오늘 나에게 1위를 달라고.
Oh.
오.
Do you have eye drops?
안약이 있나요?
Should I stick some in your eyes for you?
당신을 위해 당신의 눈에 좀 발라드릴까요?
Never mind.
괜찮아요.
Ah, what should I do when I get the prize money?
아, 어떡해야 하지? 상금은 언제 받나요?
[Taehan Liquor 1st in-house beer brand contest awards ceremony]
[대한주류 자체 1위 맥주 브랜드 콘테스트 시상식]
- Everyone stay seated. - Who's won the first place?
- 다들 자리에 앉아 계세요. - 누가 1위를 차지했나요?
Se Hyeon, heard anything?
세현아, 뭐 들었어?
No, I haven't either.
아니요, 저도 마찬가지입니다.
Huh?
뭐?
Oh! Thank you.
오! 감사합니다.
I dedicate this award to my beloved wife and my kids.
이 상을 바칩니다 사랑하는 아내와 아이들에게.
Oh, this doesn't seem right.
아, 이건 옳지 않은 것 같아요.
Someone might think you actually won first place.
누군가는 생각할 수도 있겠네요 당신이 실제로 1위를 차지했어요.
But didn't they say getting selected means a guaranteed promotion?
그런데 선발된다고 하지 않았나요? 보장된 프로모션을 의미하나요?
Ah, I really should throw a beef party for our little ones.
아 진짜 던져야겠다 우리 꼬맹이들을 위한 쇠고기 파티.
Even friends at other companies keep asking about it lately.
다른 회사 친구들도 요즘 계속 물어봐요.
If I knew it would grow this big, I would have entered too.
이렇게까지 커질 줄 알았더라면 나도 들어갔을 텐데.
So you should've done well earlier.
그러니까 좀 더 일찍 잘했어야 했는데.
What's the point regretting now?
지금 후회하면 무슨 소용이 있나요?
Manager, aren't you excited?
매니저님, 신나지 않으세요?
Right, you even stayed late because of this and worked so hard.
그렇죠, 늦게까지 계셨군요 그것 때문에 정말 열심히 일했다.
Seems like I was really desperate for it after so long.
정말 그랬던 것 같아 너무 오랜만이어서 필사적입니다.
But after giving it my all, I feel more relieved than hopeful.
하지만 내 모든 것을 바친 후에는 기대보다는 안도감을 느낀다.
Me too.
저도요.
It would be amazing if our team got 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place, right?
우리 팀이라면 정말 좋을 것 같아요. 1위, 2위, 3위를 차지했죠?
- I'm getting first, right? - Huh?
- 내가 먼저 갈 거지? - 뭐?
- What? What is it? - What? Why?
- 무엇? 그것은 무엇입니까? - 무엇? 왜?
Imagination is free, after all.
결국 상상은 자유입니다.
Hey, Kim Tak Soo!
안녕하세요, 김탁수님!
[Taehan Liquor in-house beer brand contest awards ceremony]
[대한주류 사내 맥주 브랜드 콘테스트 시상식]
Thank you for waiting.
기다려주셔서 감사합니다.
Then, starting now,
그럼 이제부터,
we'll begin the Taehan Liquor contest awards ceremony to find the next Try beer.
대한주 콘테스트를 시작하겠습니다 다음을 찾는 시상식 맥주를 마셔보세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Taehan Liquor's President, Kang Du Jun, will present the awards.
대한주류 강두준 대표이사. 상을 발표할 예정이다.
Please welcome him
그를 환영해주세요
with a big round of applause.
큰 박수로.
He's so handsome.
그는 너무 잘생겼어요.
Kang Du Jun! Kang Du Jun!
강두준! 강두준!
Hello, I'm Kang Du Jun.
안녕하세요 강두준입니다.
Thank you all for showing so much interest in this contest.
보여주신 모든분들께 감사드립니다 이번 콘테스트에 많은 관심 부탁드립니다.
Through this opportunity, I've been able to feel the talent and passion of our employees,
이번 기회를 통해 제가 할 수 있었던 건 직원들의 재능과 열정을 느껴보세요.
and it's been a rewarding time for me as well.
정말 유익한 시간이었습니다 나에게도 마찬가지다.
I will now announce the winners.
이제 당첨자를 발표하겠습니다.
[3rd Place]
[3위]
Third place.
세 번째 장소.
Assistant Manager Choi Jong Seo from the PR team.
최종서 대리 홍보팀에서요.
Oh my, it's you!
맙소사, 바로 당신이에요!
Next, I'll announce second place.
다음으로 2위를 발표하겠습니다.
Manager Kim Min Jae from the Sales Team.
영업팀 김민재 과장.
[2nd Place]
[2위]
[1st Place]
[1위]
Now, only the long-awaited first place remains.
이제 기다리던 일만 남았습니다 1위가 남아있습니다.
The first prize will be 30 million won and the chance to launch their own product.
1등상금은 3천만원 그리고 자신만의 제품을 출시할 수 있는 기회도 얻었습니다.
Please announce the first-place winner.
1등 당첨자를 발표해주세요.
Yes, I will announce first place.
네, 1위를 발표하겠습니다.
[1st Place]
[1위]
First place
1위
goes to the New Product Development Team's
신제품개발팀으로 갑니다
Manager Jang Hui Won, congratulations.
장희원 매니저님, 축하드립니다.
Congratulations! Congratulations!
축하해요! 축하해요!
Well done!
잘하셨어요!
Good work!
잘했어요!
[1st Place]
[1위]
That's enough, that's enough.
그 정도면 충분해요.
Hold it!
기다려라!
I have an objection to the contest results.
나는 콘테스트 결과에 이의가 있습니다.
I apologize, but during the judging process,
죄송합니다만, 심사 과정에서
allegations have surfaced that President Kang Du Jun
의혹이 표면화됐다 강두준 회장님
gave special treatment to a specific participant.
특별대우를 해주었다 특정 참가자에게.
- What? - What is she saying?
- 무엇? - 그 사람이 무슨 말을 하는 거죠?
That's absurd. In this judging process, I...
그것은 터무니없는 일입니다. 이번 심사과정에서 저는...
That female employee President Kang Du Jun is seeing.
그 여직원 강두준 회장님이 보고 계십니다.
He deliberately gave first place to that employee.
일부러 준거네 그 직원이 1등이에요.
What?
무엇?
- Oh, my. - Is it real?
- 아, 이런. - 진짜인가요?
Du Jun.
두준.
No matter what, you should have separated business from personal matters.
무슨 일이 있어도 당신은 가지고 있어야합니다 업무와 개인 문제를 분리합니다.
Don't you agree, sister-in-law?
동의하지 않나요, 며느리?
- Sister-in-law? - They're in-laws?
- 형수요? - 며느리야?
- What? - No way!
- 무엇? - 안 돼요!
- Jeez. - How?
- 이런. - 어떻게?
That woman is Manager Jang?
그 여자가 장과장이에요?
- Then... - I mean they are...
- 그럼... - 내 말은, 그들은...
The President and her...
대통령과 그녀...
Oh, my.
아, 이런.
Goodness.
선량.
Watch out!
조심하세요!
- What happened? - It fell!
- 무슨 일이에요? - 떨어졌어요!
Is he hurt?
그 사람이 다쳤나요?
- Oh no! - What do we do?
- 안 돼! - 우리는 무엇을 하나요?
Call! Call 911!
부르다! 911에 전화하세요!
I'm on it.
나는 그것에 있습니다.
- Call them! - Stay calm.
- 전화해! - 침착하세요.
Will you be alright?
괜찮으시겠어요?
I feel relieved.
나는 안도감을 느낀다.
I have nothing to hide.
나는 숨길 것이 없습니다.
I heard she's even pregnant?
그 사람도 임신했다고 들었는데?
She's really something else.
그녀는 정말 다른 사람입니다.
I'm fine. The truth will come out eventually.
잘 지내요. 진실은 결국 밝혀질 것입니다.
Do you know she's putting together a new board?
당신은 알고 있나요 그 사람이 새 보드를 만들고 있다고요?
Kang Du Jun!
강두준!
Whether I received preferential treatment or not is something you need to clarify.
내가 우대를 받았는지 여부 아닌지는 명확히 해야 할 사항입니다.
Just pretend nothing happened.
아무 일도 일어나지 않은 척하세요.
I'll pin it on misconduct anyway.
어쨌든 부정행위에 대해서는 고발하겠습니다.
Your name's right there
네 이름이 바로 거기 있어
[Taehan Liquor in-house contest judge] on the list of attendees.
[대한주류 사내 공모전 심사위원] 참석자 명단에 있습니다.
And did the Vice Chairman say he'd cover everything up again?
그리고 부회장이 말했지? 그 사람이 또 모든 걸 은폐하겠다고?
Should I greet first?
먼저 인사를 해야 할까요?
I'll make sure to lead Taehan Liquor well, so don't worry.
내가 꼭 이끌어줄게 대한술은 잘 있으니 걱정하지 마세요.